easyadbucks.com 2010-05-17

# Privacy Policy for Using EasyAdBucks.com

**Information Collected**  
We have created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our serious commitment to your privacy. We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is used to gather broad demographic information. 

EasyAdBucks uses cookies to make sure that you get credit for any referrals you send to us, to deliver content specific to your interests, to save your password so you don't have to re-enter it when you re-visit, and for other purposes. 

Our registration form requires you to give us contact information (your name, address, and e-mail address). We use this to send information about our company, to send you e-mail advertisements, and for verification & accounting purposes. 

You may opt-out of receiving future mailings if you desire; see the choice/opt-out section below. Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We use this data to tailor the visitor's experience, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences. We collect personal off-line information for the sole purpose of paying affiliates for earnings from our program. This site contains links to other sites. 

EasyAdBucks is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of websites not within the www.easyadbucks.com domain. 

EasyAdBucks uses a sign-up form for new affiliates and advertisers. We collect visitor's contact information (e-mail address, physical address, name & phone number). The member's contact information is used to get in touch with the member when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. 

**Public Forums**  
EasyAdBucks, may make chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

**Security**  
EasyAdBucks has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. If something happens that is beyond our control, we can not be held responsible for leaked member info. However, rest assured, this hasn't happened yet and we don't expect it to. 

**Children's Guidelines**  
We do not collect online contact information without prior parental consent or parental notification, which will include an opportunity for the parent to prevent use of the information and participation in the activity. Without prior parental consent, online information will only be used to respond directly to the child's request and will not be used for other purposes without prior parental consent. We do not collect personally identifiable off-line contact information without prior parental consent. We do not distribute to third parties any personally identifiable information. We do not give the ability to publicly post or otherwise distribute personally identifiable contact information. We do not entice by the prospect of a special game, prize or other activity, to divulge more information than is needed to participate in the activity. 

**Choice/Opt-Out**  
EasyAdBucks provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us at the point where we request information about the visitor. 

We give our users the following options for removing their information from our database: 

  * [Click Here](http://www.easyadbucks.com/pages/userinfo.php) to access your profile page. At the bottom of the page you will find the option to "Cancel Account". (Logging in is required). 
  * You may also [Contact Us](http://www.easyadbucks.com/pages/contact.php) and request your affiliateship to be canceled at anytime.

**Correct/Update**  
EasyAdBucks gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided: 

  * Affiliates Area - log-in and change your personal information.
  * Contact Us - you can use our contact forum, live chat, forums, phone support, or any other methods to request a chance on your account.

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with EasyAdBucks, you can [Contact Us](http://www.easyadbucks.com/pages/contact.php).
